[{"question":"Resistive touch sensor is used for longer time than capacitive touch sensor.","answers":{"a":"True","b":"False"},"correctAnswer":"a"},
{"question":"The physical quantity that is measured by a touch sensor is","answers":{"a":"Pressure","b":"Volume","c":"Area","d":"Density"},"correctAnswer":"a"},
{"question":"Smallest change which a sensor can detect is","answers":{"a":"Resolution","b":"Accuracy","c":"Precision","d":"Scale"},"correctAnswer":"a"},
{"question":"The working of touch sensor is similar to","answers":{"a":"Magnetic switches","b":"Simple switches","c":"Limit switches","d":"Level switches"},"correctAnswer":"b"},
{"question":"What factors will increase the capacitance of capacitive touch sensor?","answers":{"a":"If the area of electrode is larger and thickness of cover material is smaller.","b":"If the area of electrode is larger and thickness of cover material is larger.","c":"If the area of electrode is smaller and thickness of cover material is smaller.","d":"If the area of electrode is smaller and thickness of cover material is larger."},"correctAnswer":"a"},
{"question":"Which material is enough to trigger the load in a capacitive touch sensor without any external force?","answers":{"a":"Dielectric material","b":"Semi conductive material","c":"Both a & b","d":"None of these"},"correctAnswer":"b"},
{"question":"An insulator is applied with a conductive coating on which type of capacitive touch sensor?","answers":{"a":"Surface capacitive sensing","b":"Projected capacitive sensing","c":"Both a & b","d":"None of these"},"correctAnswer":"a"},
{"question":"What is the use of IC in projected capacitive sensing?","answers":{"a":"To amplify conductivity","b":"To charge and monitor the grid","c":"To regulate resistance","d":"To discharge the grid"},"correctAnswer":"b"},
{"question":"Which touch screen is coated with a transparent material?","answers":{"a":"Capacitive touch screen","b":"SAW","c":"Infrared","d":"Resistive touch screen"},"correctAnswer":"d"},
{"question":"Other name for tactile sensor is","answers":{"a":"Pressure sensor","b":"Humidity sensor","c":"Touch sensor","d":"Temperature sensor"},"correctAnswer":"c"}]